[{"answer": "What", "docId": "Bringing-Out-the-Dead.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "my friend, play the my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You told me he was dead. Flatline", "docId": "Bringing-Out-the-Dead.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I hate pronouncing people dead over the phone.  Better, huh? They're fixed and dilated. He's plant food", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " It's my friend. my friend Smith", "docId": "Bringing-Out-the-Dead.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "It's my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "She's the daughter of a cardiac arrest I brought in last night. I told her we'd give her a ride back to Misery. Her father's showing signs of improving", "docId": "Bringing-Out-the-Dead.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I'm hungry too. We gotta get some food after this", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "That's how it's done. You have to keep the body going until the brain and heart recover enough to go on their own", "docId": "Bringing-Out-the-Dead.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " He's better", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "My father was a great man, you know. There was nobody he wouldn't help. You know that crazy guy my friend who I gave water to last night? He lived in our house for almost a year. A total stranger he'd do anything for, his own family though ..", "docId": "Bringing-Out-the-Dead.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Not as good as Nino's", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yeah, or Saint my friend. You from the neighborhood", "docId": "Bringing-Out-the-Dead.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "On yeah? I went to Holy Name. Where'd you go to high school", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I think I'd remember that", "docId": "Bringing-Out-the-Dead.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Mostly. It must be my face. My mother always said I looked like a priest", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Rule number on", "docId": "Bringing-Out-the-Dead.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You don't know the first thing about rule number three, cannot begin to understand the complexities of that rule. Come on, let's go look at some hookers. The Kit my friend will be letting out.  Don't ever call a junkie whore a crackhead. They get real mad", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "In that time, you ever have sex", "docId": "Bringing-Out-the-Dead.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "No underwear", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Don't give me that look", "docId": "Bringing-Out-the-Dead.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You know what I'm talking about. It's all over your face. That ", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " I'll drink to that", "docId": "Bringing-Out-the-Dead.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " Greatest job in the world", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "It's okay, my friend. Come on in", "docId": "Bringing-Out-the-Dead.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "He's not a cop, he's a medic.  I'm CY my friend", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " These are hard times, my friend", "docId": "Bringing-Out-the-Dead.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Great to be drunk. Sobriety's killing me", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Let's break something, my friend. Let's bust something, bomb something", "docId": "Bringing-Out-the-Dead.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " I don't kno", "qsentId": 30}]